<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Defeat The Troll</string>
    <string name="splash_text">Greetings, human! Come to do battle with a troll again, eh? How spiffing. Choose your method of troll defeat!</string>
    <string name="meme_btn_text">Memes</string>
    <string name="axe_btn_txt">Axe</string>
    <string name="meme_splash_text">So, you chose memes.\nThe good news: Trolls are weak towards memes.\nThe bad news: The troll is woefully out of touch. Proceed accordingly.\nThe Troll is browsing the internet, using Internet Explorer; they laugh, saying \"Haha, that cat wants to haz cheezburger!\" Your phone at the ready, hit him with your best meme.</string>
    <string name="show_meme_btn_txt">Show Meme</string>
    <string name="play_again_btn_txt">Play Again?</string>
    <string name="victory_splash_txt">Congratulations, you defeated the Troll!</string>
    <string name="defeat_splash_txt">In Soviet Russia, you defeat Troll! Here though, you die.</string>
    <string name="meme_loss_txt">The troll proves the age old adage, "If your memes aren't funny, a troll will rip you limb from limb." Better luck next time!</string>
    <string name="meme_win_txt">The troll has laughed himself to death, improbably. Good job, memelord.</string>
    <string name="generic_error">Hmmm, that didn\'t really jive, try again perchance?</string>
    <string name="duplicate_meme_txt">You\'ve shown the Troll that meme before; He\'s not impressed</string>
    <string name="meme_low_dmg_txt">You don\'t get the feeling the troll found that terribly funny...</string>
    <string name="meme_med_dmg_txt">The Troll laughs, clearly appreciating your meme.</string>
    <string name="meme_high_dmg_txt">The Troll laughs and laughs, slapping it\'s knee. I guess you could call it a real...funny meme!</string>
    <string name="meme_negative_dmg_txt">The Troll suddenly looks angry, and tells you to get back in your basement!</string>
    <string name="axe_splash_txt">You chose \"Axe\". As in, the thing the Troll is most likely to kill you with. Okay Zoomer, let\'s see if you can end up dead here.</string>
    <string name="axe_sel_prompt_txt">Choose your axe:</string>
    <string name="action_sel_prompt_txt">Each round, choose to either attack or defend; successfully defending means you take no damage, and deal a small amount of damage in return, while attacking obviously damages the Troll the most, but you could die very quickly.</string>
    <string name="war_axe_btn_txt">War Axe</string>
    <string name="peace_axe_btn_txt">Peace Axe</string>
    <string name="war_and_peace_axe_btn_txt">War and Peace Axe</string>
    <string name="attack_btn_txt">Attack</string>
    <string name="defend_btn_txt">Defend</string>
    <string name="quest_btn_txt">Quest</string>
    <string name="quest_prompt_txt">Very well, human, a quest it shall be.\nAs you journey, you will gain keywords that will effect your choices; choose wisely!</string>
    <string name="Continue_btn_txt">Continue</string>
    <string name="keywords_prefix">Keywords:\n</string>
</resources>
